{\clip(190,219,190,219)\t(0,600,\clip(100,217,280,220))\t(16600,17100,\clip(190,217,190,220))}m 0 0 m 180 1 l 0 1 l 0 0 l 180 0
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}翻\h译
胡瀚引\h\h\hBBSsure\h\h\h思GOOH!\h\h\hHelado
leoginos\h\h\h村口牛哥\h\h\h\hShirleeC
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}校对\h&\h后期
ntpooh\h\h\h\h你以为列
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}总监
大红
片头推广合作洽谈\h请联系普罗米修斯邮箱\hPLMXS2016@GmaiL.com
-五秒钟  -在这个人之后
- Five seconds. - After this person.
-现在没人了  -还有
- And clear. - Not clear.
-去吧  -不行
- Go. - No.
就是现在
Now.
邮局
这应该是现金
This could be cash.
不  应该是汇票
No. Money order.
类似与支票
二十的
Twenty.
我想他们卖这玩意在
Oh, I think they sell these at...
我有那里的收据可以用
I have a receipt that'll work for this.
玩偶游戏  12.99美元  得到
Hmm. Toys and games. 12.99, Target.
轻松返现
Easy return.
这可不是条便宜的领带
So, this is, this is not a cheap tie.
你可看不出来  你的出生可没那么富贵
Well, you can't see it, because you're not of gentle birth.
那是空的
It's empty!
《亿万富翁》
奥尔西娅和维克多·杨
Althea and Victor Young.
拉德拉高地 幽谷集市街4305号
4305 Fairglen Road, Ladera Heights.
我们可以乘2路
Oh. We could take the 2.
从这到那里
It goes there from here.
我们还有时间
We got time.
把天主教式的女学生服穿上
Um, do the Catholic schoolgirl costume.
因为这样更能博得同情
'Cause you've got some heartstrings to pull.
要记住  不要索要回报
And remember, don't ask for a reward.
让他们自己给你
Just let them come to you.
-你带着表对吧  -对
- You got the watch, right? - Yeah.
看看这个
Wow. Look at this.
它就在那里  我差点踩到它
It was just right there. I almost stepped on it.
一直以来  它就在那里
All this time, it was just right there.
是的
Yeah.
你是要去圣心大学吗
Do you go to Sacred Heart?
我们的女儿杰尼读过圣心大学
Our daughter Jenny went to Sacred Heart.
来  进来吃点曲奇吧
Here, let's have you in for a Coke.
我一直都相信有天使存在
I've always believed in angels.
我可没有  只有她是这样
Not me. That's her thing.
这是什么
What's this?
一张礼券
It's a gift certificate.
他们的女儿是个按摩师
Their daughter's a masseuse.
"不要主动索取回报"是A计划
"Don't ask for a reward" was plan A.
B计划是"索要回报"
Plan B was "ask for a reward."
有钱人有时也会非常的小气
Rich people can be very cheap sometimes.
他们一直不停地说他们的女儿
They were talking about her nonstop.
她在柠檬香膏工作  她上过大学
She works at Mélisse, she went to college...
柠檬香膏
Mélisse?
他们说得都入迷了  让人很不舒服
They were obsessed. It was creepy.
那是洛杉矶最贵的餐馆
That's the most expensive restaurant in L.A.
-她只是在那工作  -就算她只在那工作
- She just works there. - Well, uh, even to work there,
你需要变有钱
you have to be rich.
-我认为  -等一下  等等
- Oh. I mean, I... - Wait a minute. Wait.
二分之一幽谷集市街4305号
4305 1/2 Fairglen Road.
4  4503  二分之一幽谷集市街
4... 4503 1/2 Fairglen...
你  你刚刚在那里
You-you were just... Well, you were just there.
但这  这座房子就那里的正后方
But th-this is, this is the house right behind it.
-这东西值钱  -是的  是的
- This is worth money. - Yeah. Yeah.
-看  这有美元的符号  -是啊
- See, dollar signs. - Yeah.
这  这个
This-this...
这种高端的服务  你懂吧
This type of high-end, uh... you know.
-这很好  是啊  -这能值200或300美元
- It's good. Yeah. - It's worth $200 or $300.
是啊
Yeah.
好吧
Okay, um...
等等
Wait.
换成现金
Cash refund.
好吧  如果按现金返还能
Okay. What about a percentage
还总价值百分之几
of the total value?
比如说按总价值的75%
Like 75% of the total value.
不  不  这不是这样
No. No, that's not how...
请问一下
I'm sorry.
你是怎么  你是怎么知道我的父母的
How do you, how do you know my parents?
或者换东西怎么样  比如那个石头
Or what about an exchange, um, for that rock?
-不行  -不行  好吧
- No. - No? Okay.
那这些怎么样
Mm-mm. What about these?
不行  明白了
No? Understood.
这个  这个  这个架子
This. This, uh, this shelf.
这是我的底线了  因为它并不
And that's gonna be my final, because it's just...
它不值多少钱  我其实是
it's not worth very much and I'm gonna be
吃  吃亏了
taking a loss on-on...
要是我不按摩
...on the massage.
我要拿走这个
I'll take that.
你不想要按摩  对吗
Well, you don't want a massage, right?
这个一般要多少时间
How long does this usually take?
你的是一个钟头的券  所以
Uh, your gift certificate is for 60 minutes, so...
不  不用
Oh. N-no.
我不需要  能不能
I-I don't need, um... could...
我们能在20分钟内按完吗
Do you think we could do it in 20?
可以
Okay.
要是劲太大了就告诉我
So just tell me if it's too much pressure.
劲太大了
It's too much pressure.
-这样好些了吗  -太大
- Is this better? - Too much.
那这样呢
How about this?
这样可以了吗
Is that better?
可以了
Yeah.
嗨  我们是跟她一起的
Hi. We're with her.
已经过了好一会了  所以
It was taking a while, so...
不能返还现金
No refund?
不能  礼券不返还现金  但我们要按完了
No. I don't refund gifts, but we're almost done.
她只想要20分钟的服务
She only wanted 20 minutes.
我们能用另外的40分钟换那个石头吗
Okay, can we have that rock for the other 40 minutes?
今天我们已经用六个不同的名字
We won the Vitafusion giveaway
拿到了小熊糖赠品
under six different names today.
还有道奇蝰蛇GT跑车的抽奖
Oh. And the Motor Trend Dodge Viper GT Sweepstakes.
-这还有个免费的遮阳板  -小的正在爆掉
- That's a free visor. - The little ones are popping!
砰砰砰
Pop, pop, pop!
他们全都在爆
They're all popping!
给我停下  好吗
Just st-stop. Hey. Okay?
谁负责这个
Who's in charge of the, um...
一个有扣带运动水壶  不含双酚A
A sport water bottle, BPA-free, with a carabiner.
我们以前应该没有拿到过这个
Huh. I don't think we've won that before.
以星期三来说不算太糟
Not bad for a Wednesday.
嘿  你
Hey, yo!
嘿  等等
Hey. Hey!
嘿  伙计们
Hey, you guys?
我有
I h...
-我有份工作  -快他妈把嘴闭上
- I have a job. - Shut the fuck up.
继续走  快走
Keep walking, keep walking. Ah.
-靠  -二月
- Fuck. - February?
三月  四月
March? April?
快点  兄弟  这个箱子是空的
Come on, man, this tank's empty.
我们也许得分期付款
Uh, we may have to pay in installments.
-分期  不  -是的
- In install... No. - Yeah.
不  不分  房租就是分期付款
No! No install... I mean, rent is an installment.
它就是按月分期付款的
It's a monthly installment.
我们明天早上就会有钱的  所有的
We'll have it in the morning. All...
二月  三月  四月  一共1500
February, March, April, all 1,500.
刚刚  对  刚刚我们在
Just, uh... yeah, we were just,
刚刚我们正在谈工作呢
we were just talking about a job right now.
-就在刚才  -对
- We were, just now.  - Yeah.
-你们一个月只用付500  -但房子有漏
- You only pay 500 a month? - But it leaks.
那很容易搞定  很好搞定
It's very manageable. Very manageable.
它只是在固定的日子漏
It's... it leaks on-on a schedule.
你  你之后会清理墙的  对吧
Y-You're patting down the wall afterwards, right?
-当然  -那很好
- Oh, yeah. - That's good.
潮湿会造成腐烂
The dampness becomes rot,
然后整栋楼都会塌掉
and then the whole building collapses.
嘿  你能把压缩机打开吗
Hey, fire up that compressor, will you?
代价是很高的
Very expensive.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
这是我的问题
It's my condition.
-他有  -我  我没过滤器
- He's got a... - I mean, I-I have no filters.
这没什么大不了的
It's no big deal.
当我没说
Ignore it.
明天早上再见
See you in the morning.
好的  再见
Okay, we'll see you.
另一边
The other side!
我要去上一门课
Uh, I-I'm supposed to take this class.
这是我作为社工必须要上的课
It's a required thing by my caseworker,
但我有一点点忙
but I'm kind of in the midst of something,
所以要是她能去的话
so if she could just go, there's...
这有张报名表
there's a sign-up sheet.
求你们了  我  我知道你们干这种事
Come on. I-I know you guys do this stuff.
跟他们谈酬金
Tell them about the money!
我可以付20美元
I can pay $20.
你听到了
You heard?
听得到了  但关于这个
Yeah, well, what about the...
对啊  非常紧急我们要快点去
Yeah, so hurry up so we can go.
谢谢
Thanks.
-我喜欢你的  -好
- I like your... - Yeah.
你叫什么
What's your name?
凯莉
Kelli.
你叫什么
What's your name?
只是为了填在登记表上
It's for the sign-up sheet.
好吧
Oh.
全名是凯莉·法因
It's Kelli Fain.
凯莉里面有个字母"I"  F-A-I-N
Kelli with an "I," F-A-I-N.
你都不用进去
You don't even have to go in.
只要拿到黄色的纸条就可以回来了
Just get the yellow slip and come right back.
姓法因
Oh, Fain.
我需要一个黄色的纸条
I need a yellow slip.
好的  多琳达会给你的
Okay. Dorinda can give you that.
她在里面
Uh, she's inside.
积极育儿
我们开始得有些晚了
We're starting a little late.
也许改了时间让某些人失望了
Maybe the time change threw some people off.
-现在请坐下  -但只有两次
- L-Let's take a seat, please. - But it's only twice.
-这是你的纸条  -谢谢  多琳达
- Well, here's your slip. Okay. - Thanks, Dorinda.
坐吧
Have a seat.
我们开始了
Let's get started.
如果你需要多琳达那的社工收条
If you need a caseworker receipt from Dorinda,
你可以待会休息的时候去拿
you can get it later at the break.
好
Okay.
两边都在传工作表
There are worksheets coming from both directions.
拿一张然后往旁边传
Uh, take one and pass it down.
-能传一下吗  -蓝色的是
- Could you pass it? - The blue one is
我昨天给你们提到过的营养表
the nutrition cheat sheet that I mentioned to you yesterday.
请看着粉色的这张
Please take a look at the pink sheet,
最上面写着"母乳爬行"的这张
the one that says "The Breast Crawl" on top.
能放一下录像带吗
Will you start the tape, please?
谢谢
Thank you.
好  这太棒了
Okay, this is great.
这就是母婴联系在起作用
This is the mother-baby bond at work.
如果新生儿马上放到
If the newborn is immediately placed
母亲的肚子上
on the mother's abdomen,
他能自己爬到乳房去
he makes his way all the way to the breast all by himself.
但如果把婴儿放到婴儿床上
Now, if a baby's placed on a cot,
婴儿的死亡率会升高
the infant mortality goes up.
母婴之间的联系会减弱
The bonding goes down.
乳汁的分泌会减少
The lactation goes down.
我们昨天讲的重要的东西
All that important stuff that we talked about yesterday.
还记得吗
You remember?
当婴儿一接近乳头就会张开嘴
Baby's mouth opens as he approaches the nipple.
母婴之间的连接从这里开始
And the bonding begins.
我去  姐妹  你在干什么  登记吗
Shit, girl, what'd you do, enroll?
我错过了什么
What did I miss?
母乳爬行和
Uh, the... breast crawl and...
是的  我就要做那个
Oh, yeah. I'm gonna do that.
很酷呢
That's cool, huh?
不  你不会想那样来照料的
No, you don't want to baby it like that.
那会  会
It'll-it'll get all...
感谢您的等候
Thank you for waiting.
即将为您转接人工服务
Someone will be with you shortly.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
抱歉
Sorry, uh...
我只是
I just...
我们中了一票大的  但是用不了
We won something big, but we can't use it.
是豪华度假游
Uh, it's the Ooh La Luxe getaway.
是去纽约市的头等舱双飞旅行
It's a first-class trip for two to the Big Apple,
the Big Apple：美国纽约市的别称
也可以改成三张不可退换的长途汽车票
and it's redeemable for three nonrefundable coach tickets.
-你坐不了飞机  -我知道
- You'll never fly. - I know.
所以  或许我们
So, maybe we...
那是什么
What is that?
班上的男人给我的
Guy at the class gave me them.
你  你想要一个吗
Do... Do you want one?
当一个男人给你木头
When a man gives you wood,
或者各种木头制品时
anything made out of wood,
他是在说  "你要让我勃起"
he's saying, "You give me wood."
我去过纽约
I've been to New York.
你和我可以一起去  就我们两个
You and I could go together, just the two of us.
像一次
Like a...
母女旅行
mother-daughter getaway.
你好  斯托维克
Oh, hey, Stovik.
你好啊
There you are.
夹克很棒
That's a great jacket.
泡沫清下来了吗
You pat it down?
是的
Yeah.
特雷泽  我
Oh, Theresa, I... Oh.
其余部分很快就有了
Uh, the rest is coming.
我们还得赶路  我们先
Uh, we're just on our way. We have to, uh...
-这是什么东西  -这是一张汇票
- What is this? - Ah, that's a money order.
泡泡工厂
跟钱一样  二十块
Same as money. $20.
我们得去看一下邮件  然后
We have to check our mail, and, uh...
好吧  那个啊
Well... Oh, that.
至于那个  我觉得那个值五十块
Now, see, that... I think that's worth 50...
这招现在行不通了
Not this time.
啥
Wha...?
我再也受不了了
I can't do this anymore.
你在哭吗
Are you crying?
我得把那处泄漏补好
I'm patching the leak.
我要驱逐你们
I'm evicting you.
我可以用那间房子赚一万美金  懂吗
I can get $10,000 for this space, you understand?
一万美金
$10,000.
我们有个孩子
We have a child.
那面墙是海绵做的  海绵啊
That wall is a sponge. It's a sponge.
那栋楼该受到谴责  讲真
This building ought to be condemned, really.
我们可以  我们可以举报它
We could, we could report it
举报到卫生和公共服务部
to the Department of Health and Human Services!
啥
What?
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay.
让  让我们住到周五就行
Just-just, just give us till Friday.
你会收到一千五百块现金
You'll have 1,500 in cash bills.
我们在周五前就能赚到
We'll have it by Friday.
伙计  我们需要一点时间把钱凑出来
Dude, we need a little time to get it together.
明天那个周五吗
Friday tomorrow?
明天就是了吗
It's tomorrow?
那个  我不是说字面上的周五
Um, well, I didn't literally mean...
我是说  那就是个俗语
I mean, that's just a saying,
你知道的  "周五之前"
you know, "by Friday."
-那仅仅是指一个周的结束  -下周五
- It just means end of the week. - Next Friday.
是  是下周五的下周五
Uh, uh, the-the one after that.
-下下周五  -没错
- Friday after next. - Yeah.
两周
Two weeks.
该死  我们没时间到处乱跑
Shit! We don't have time to be horsing around.
那是我们最好的方法了
That was our best thing.
那新装了一个摄像头  我事先并不知道
It's a new camera. I didn't know.
太糟了
This is really bad.
一旦你的脸被照进他们的系统
Mm-hmm. Once your face is in their system,
-他们会抓到你  罚一千  抵押房产  -对
- they got you... fines, for 1K, home equity. - Yeah. Mm-hmm.
不过你也许你挺想那样  我说不准
But maybe you want all that. I don't know.
我呢  宁可溜走
Me? I prefer to just skim.
-我也是  -是吗
- So do I. - Do you?
那可有趣了
Ah, that's interesting.
因为大部分人都想成为亿万富翁
Because most people want to be kajillionaires.
这就是梦想  这就是他们让你成瘾的方式
That's the dream. That's how they get you hooked.
让你对糖上瘾  对咖啡因上瘾
Hooked on sugar, hooked on caffeine.
疯疯癫癫的
Ha-ha-ha. Cry-cry-cry.
还想母女旅行
Mother-daughter getaway.
这他妈能帮我们搞出房租吗
How the fuck does that help us get the rent?
天呐  得了吧  动动脑子
God. Come on! Think!
好吧  那么
Okay, so...
我们周三一起飞去纽约
We all fly to New York together on Wednesday,
然后我们立马装作陌生人飞回来
and then we fly right back as strangers.
因此  在行李带旁  我们要装作互不相识
So, at the baggage carousel, we don't know each other.
别  别看我
Don't-don't look at me.
行吧  我在看周围
Okay, I'm looking around.
我想确认这些是我们的包裹
I want to make sure these are our bags.
打扰一下  先生
Excuse me, sir.
这是纽约来的航班的行李箱吗
Is this the luggage for the flight from New York?
你们俩是互相认识的
You two know each other.
-我们是夫妻吗  -对
- We're a couple? - Yeah.
我明白了
Oh. I see.
我现在被当成傻瓜玩了
I am the dum-dum now.
我可是有本科学历的
I have a bachelor's degree.
她甚至连本科是什么都不知道
She doesn't even know what that is.
接着你不小心拿走了我的包然后回了家
Then you accidentally take my bags and go home.
我会留在机场报失
I'll stay at the airport and report my loss.
幸运的是  我有旅客保险
Luckily, I have traveler's insurance,
因此他们会发我一张支票  值
so they'll issue us a check for, uh, um...
1575美元  我们可以直接签给斯托维克
...$1,575, which we can just sign right over to Stovik
第二天就给他  我们提前一整周付钱
the next day and be, uh, more than a full week early.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen, uh,
我们遭遇了不稳定的气流
we're experiencing some choppy air here.
请回到座位上并系好安全带
Please return to your seats and fasten your seat belts.
为保证飞行平稳  我们将提高至十一千米
We'll be going up to 37,000 feet for a smoother ride.
好吧  快点  快点吧
Okay, come on. Come on.
行吧
Okay.
只要平稳呼吸  平稳呼吸
Just breathe normally. Just breathe normally.
没事的  说话  我们说说话  行不  说话
All right, talk. Let's talk. Okay? Talk.
我们得说点什么  随便说点
Let's say something. Just say something.
不要祈祷  天呐你在祈祷吗
Don't pray. God, are you praying?
说话就行  说话
Just talk. Talk.
好吧
Okay.
你好吗
How are you? Um...
你好吗  你的兴趣是什么
How are you? What are your interests?
-我的兴趣吗  -你的你的你的兴趣
- My interests? - Your interests. Your interests. Your interests!
-你的兴趣  快说  -我  我不知道  我不
- Your interests! Go. Go. - I-I don't know. I don't...
-你想让我说什  -我不知道
- What do you want me to... - I don't know.
说什么都行
Just say anything. Uh...
有些人认为一个新生的婴儿
Some people think that a brand-new baby,
如果  如果  如果你把他放在母亲的腹部
if you, if you, if you put it on the abdomen,
他就会本能地爬向他妈妈的乳房
it'll just automatically crawl up to the mom's breast.
但如果放在小床上  然后他就会
But if you put it on a cot, then it'll,
我猜  会哭得更凶
I guess, cry more.
但一个向乳房爬行的婴儿
But a breast crawl baby...
别再说"乳房"了
Don't say "breast."
我只是想知道  一个婴儿是怎  怎么知道
I just wonder how-how a baby would know
-怎么  哪里  -停
- how, where... - Shh. Stop.
飞机稳下来了
It's smooth now.
你刚刚说这一堆想表达什么
What was the point of all that?
他非让我说话
He told me to talk.
你怀孕了吗
Are you pregnant?
我以前爬上去了吗  还是被放在小床上了
Did I crawl up, or was I put on a cot?
回答
Answer.
没有
No.
那种事怎么可能会发生呢
How would that have even happened?
当然是放在床上
A cot.
她怀孕了吗
Is she pregnant?
没有
No.
我妈住在新泽西州
Uh, my mom lives in New Jersey.
我们不是很亲近  我是说  我们好像
We're not that close. I mean, we... like,
几乎不说话了  因为我现在住洛杉矶
hardly ever talk now that I live in L.A.
我在这差不多一年了
Uh, I've been here almost a year,
但是  想结识人们太难了
and, ugh, it's so hard to meet people.
你们也这么认为吗  好吧  还要说什么
Do you guys find that? Okay. What else?
我住在高地公园  在繁荣区上面
I live in Highland Park, above Thrive.
所以说  这就你们想听的
So, is this the kind of thing that you...
是的  一直说话就行
Yeah, just keep talking.
随便  随便  说什么都行
Anything. Anything. Uh, just anything. Um...
-好吧  -随便说  快快快
- Okay, um... - Anything. Go. Go. Go.
我是个  医师助理
I am a, uh, physician's assistant
在雪松西奈的眼科
in ophthalmology at Cedars-Sinai.
现在是这条航线的正常颠簸程度吗
Is this the normal amount of turbulence for this route?
对
Yes.
-真的吗  -完全正确
- Really? - Totally.
-这  -糟了
- It's... - Oh, no!
怎么了
What?
我以为我忘带耳机了
I thought that I forgot my headphones.
他们说过这架飞机上有没有Wi-Fi吗
Did they say that there was Wi-Fi on this plane?
忘了
I don't remember.
有啊  你得付钱
Oh, there is. Oh, you got to pay.
-他们干嘛要收钱啊  -你最好远离它
- Why do they do that? - You're better off.
这个吗  我明白
Oh, this? Oh, I know.
说出来你可能不信  我睡觉都离不开它
Trust me, I'm the worst. I, like, sleep with it.
它就像我的第三只手
It's like my third arm.
它是个工具
It's a tool.
它本来是部队和
It was originally designed by and for the military
情报机构开发和使用的
and the intelligence community.
特别是CIA和陆军地面部队
The CIA and Army ground ops, specifically.
它很有用但是个危险的工具
It is powerful and it's a dangerous tool.
你没有手机吗
You don't have a cell phone?
我只使用它原本的功能
I use it as it was intended.
也不给它打扮
And I don't dress it up
更不会跟它玩
and play dolly with it.
那么  可千万别遇上我妈  她呢
Well, then don't meet my mom. She is... whew!
她一直在玩手机
She is always on her phone.
我是说  差不多  整天泡在手机上
I'm talking about, like, always on her phone.
-太好了  -这是您的
- Oh! Yes! - Here you are.
-螺丝起子是她的  -我不想喝  我
- Screwdriver for her. - I don't want it. I...
♪ 金酒汤力水  天生是一对 ♪
♪ Gin and tonic, gin and tonic. ♪
拿着  把那小罐罐打开  好
Here, open up that bad boy. Okay.
-谢谢  -不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
相信我  这个很有帮助  干杯
Trust me, this will help a lot. Salud.
Salud西班牙语
我只是在担心我们可能不能
Um, my only concern is that we won't be
在真正的紧急情况下思考得足够清楚
thinking clearly enough in the event of a real emergency.
-有可能会  -你是不是
- It's possible. - Oh, are you...?
我姨妈有个阿曼派的朋友
My aunt has a friend who's Amish.
该派强调道德戒律  维系原初生活状况  与现代社会保持距离
阿曼派  从基督教新教门诺派分裂而出的保守派别
不  我们不是阿曼派的
No, we're not Amish.
我们会碰酒精
We use alcohol. Oh.
当我们受伤的时候  用来麻醉止痛
When we're injured, to numb the pain.
好吧  这听起来很阿曼
Okay, that sounds Amish.
听着  我知道这有很多区别
Look, I know there's a lot of discrimination.
我朋友以前在贵格会的学校上学
My friend used to go to a Quaker school.
贵格会：宗教教派之一
让我继
And let me...
这可真是太巧了
That's super random. Uh...
好吧
Uh, oh. Okay!
很好  干了干了
All right! Chug, chug.
咕噜咕噜咕噜咕噜咕噜
Chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug.
看看这派对已经开始了
Look at this party started.
你从没在普罗维登斯待过吗
You never lived in Providence?
我从没有过
I never did.
真奇怪
It's so weird.
那边有个女孩看起来
There's a girl there who looks just...
他在盯着你的衬衫看
He's staring at your... blouse.
我知道  没问题
Oh, I know. I can handle it.
好了  各位
Okay. All right, everybody.
检查一下你们的口袋
Check your pockets.
-这也许只是声东击西  -什么
- It may be a bait and switch. - A what?
分散你的注意力
A distraction.
他可能是个扒手
He might be a pickpocket.
-你是说小偷吗  -是的
- You mean a thief? - Yeah.
刚才并没有发生那种事
That-that is, that is not what just happened.
你不懂那些事
You don't know about these things.
我不  不
I don't... No.
这种事每天都会在我身上发生
This happens to me, like, every day.
什么
What?
那么  你们是做什么工作的
So... what is it that you guys do?
拜托  你们可是知道我的一切啊  对吗
Oh, come on. You know everything about me, right?
知道我住在哪里  我奶奶的名字
You know where I live and what my grandma's name is.
所以  你们是干什么的
So, like, what are, what are you,
做什么工作  教授吗
what are you guys, like... professors?
是滴
Yep.
是吗  好吧  猜的真准
Yeah? Well, that was a really great guess.
不
No.
不  你不是的
No, you're not.
你看起来就像
You're, like, um...
你认为自己是个可靠的人吗
Would you consider yourself a trustworthy person?
-你有那种品质吗  -无需回答
- Is that one of your qualities? - You don't have to answer that.
有的
Yes.
我们要在机场办件大事
We have something very big happening at the airport.
天啊  我就知道你们在搞什么鬼
Oh, my God, I knew you guys were up to something.
我们两个人  却有三件行李
All right, there's two of us and there's three bags.
你知道我要说什么了吗
Do you see where I'm going with this?
完全不知道
Not at all.
你拿了吗  真的吗  放回去
You took it? Really? Put it back.
好的
Oh, yeah.
我  我  我感觉到了
I-I-I feel it. I...
-真的吗  -我感觉到了  我  我
- Do you? - I felt it. I-I...
好吧
Okay.
那个旧包
That old bag.
好了  好滴
Here we go. Yep.
谢谢
Thank you.
好的
All right.
最后一件了吧
Is that the last one?
-她有很多  -太多的鞋了
- She has a lot of... - Well, too many shoes.
你都拿上了吗
Oh. You got everything?
好的
Okay.
咱们走吧
Off we go.
那么  假如真丢了  我并不是说真丢了
All right, so if they are lost, and I'm not saying they are,
但一旦丢了  你有旅行险
but if they are, your traveler's insurance
可赔付您高达1575美元
covers you for up to $1,575.
只要确认丢失  你就能得到赔偿
You get that as soon as the loss is verified.
那  那需要多久
H-How long does that usually take?
很快的
Oh, they're pretty quick.
最多需要六周
Six weeks at the longest.
最  最短呢
A-And the shortest?
真的情况各异
Oh, that really varies.
但是不用担心
But don't worry.
我们很少会丢失包裹
It's really rare that we completely lose a bag.
我相信能找到的
I'm sure they'll turn up.
是的  这里很划算的
Yeah, it's a pretty good deal here.
她来了
Oh, she's here.
别担心  我能搞定
Don't worry, I got this.
女士  我带您去您的位置
Ma'am, I'll show you right to your seat.
就在那里
Just go with it.
你能从包裹那得到多少钱
How much did you get for the bags?
我大学时的那些男生也这样做过
These guys at my college used to do the same scam
在圣诞假期的时候假装丢了行李
with their luggage at Christmas vacation.
-我觉得可以得到超过  -这个  这个是
- I think you can get more... - It's-it's,
这是个原创的骗局
it's an original con.
-是我发明的 -好吧
- I invented it. - Oh, okay.
什么情况
What?
我不确定赔款能在周五前拿到
I don't know if the check will be here by Friday.
什么
What?
可能会  但是
It might, but...
也许需要等六周
it might take six weeks.
要六周吗
In six weeks?
太迟了
That's too late.
我们飞过来  我冒着生命危险来
We just flew... I just risked my life for...
对不起
Sorry.
要六周吗
In six weeks?
谁知道呢
Who knows?
也许会提前  不一定
It could come sooner. It varies.
好吧
Right.
什么会提前 支票吗
What could come sooner? The check?
赔偿金会以支票的形式邮寄至被保人
她到底是谁啊
Who even is she?
这个人怎么会有用
How is this person an asset?
我不  我不明白
I don't... I don't understand.
我还是去个洗手间吧
Maybe I'll go to the restroom.
洗手间坏了
It's broken. Huh?
你得去外面上加油站旁边那个
You have to use the one outside by the gas station.
好的
Right.
-什么事  -你终于接电话了  亲爱的
- Yes? - There you are, hon.
我一直不停地在给你打电话
I've been calling nonstop.
对不起  我调成飞行模式了
Sorry, I had it on airplane mode.
好的  所以你安全落地了吧
Oh, so... Okay. So you landed.
你到家了  真好
You're home. Good.
我正在看那个古董展览节目  你在看吗
I'm watching that antique show. Do you have it on?
是的  你  你还是睡觉去吧
Uh, yeah. You can... Why don't you go to sleep
咱们明天还可以聊
and we can just talk tomorrow or some...
你已经上床了吗  躺舒服了吗
Are you in bed, all cozy?
给膝盖下垫个羊毛枕头
Put that wool pillow under your knees.
我垫了  特别舒服
I'm using mine. It's so nice.
你有什么脆脆的好东西吃吗
You have something nice and crunchy to eat?
我看不清你的脸
I can't see your face very well.
-太黑了  -灯坏了
- It's so dark. - The light's broken.
好吧
Oh. Mm. All right.
我给你预定一盏可以粘的灯
I'm ordering you a stick-on light,
就和你旧房间里那个一样的
like the one in your old room.
好的  我知道了
Okay, I know.
哪一个呢
Just which one?
那边现在几点了
What time is it there?
咱们的时间不同步
Our schedules are so out of sync.
如果我们回去你就会好一些了
I know you'll feel better when we're aligned back,
但现在不可能的
but that's impossible now.
-是的  我 -好吧  周二可以到货
- Yeah, and I... - Okay, so it'll come Tues...
是的  周二可以到
No. Yes. Tuesday. Uh-huh.
你拿到冰茶了吗
Did you get the case of iced tea? Mm.
我今早看到些东西让我想到了你
I saw something this morning that made me think of you.
会让你感到开心的
This is gonna make you so happy.
你输入"薇茉灌溉投手"
Type in "Vemo infusion pitcher."
看底部那张照片  放大再放大
Look on the bottom picture, and then zoom in, zoom in,
然后缩放到
zoom back to... Oh!
那个男人的旧摇椅  那个价值50万
This guy's old rocking chair... it's worth a half a million.
我不知道  不
I had no idea. No.
他很惊讶  他没有
He's so surprised. He had no...
我有个能让咱们得到1500的贼招
I have a heist we can do, to get the 1,500.
好吧  我就直接说了  我开始说了  好吧
Okay, I'm just gonna start, I'm gonna start talking. Okay.
我  我并不是个助理医师
So, I'm, um... I'm not a physician's assistant.
那样说是  我都不知道为啥要那样说
That was, um... I don't even know why I said that. Anyway...
我在商业街的艾布拉姆光学配镜中心工作
I work at Abram's Optics in the Galleria,
那是个最烂的牌子  所以你估计不知道
which, if you don't know, is the worst branch there is.
说真的  在那儿工作简直是浪费生命
Honestly, I'm wasting my life there.
我整天就是给老农民们推销双光眼镜
I just sell bifocals to agro old people all day.
那些人又吝啬又极其孤独绝望
Mean but, like, also super lonely and desperate, you know?
我曾被邀请去参加复活节活动  去打麻将
Like, I've been invited to Easters and to Mahjong
去看他们的剪贴薄
and to look at scrapbooks and...
我因为觉得恶心不去  但我一旦去了
You know, I don't go because it's gross, but if I did,
我敢打赌  能发现些疯狂的古董
I bet you that I would find mad antiques.
是的
Huh. Yeah.
不一定是价值连城的古董
I mean, not super fancy ones,
但我觉得  如果我说我喜欢哪个
but I have a feeling that if I said I liked something,
他们都会免费送我或者便宜卖我
they would give it to me for free or cheap,
然后咱们就可以把那些卖了大赚一笔
and then we can sell it and turn a tidy profit.
我们把那些古董卖给谁呢
Who do we sell the antiques to?
咱们可以
We can...
咱们可以在跳蚤市场摆摊
we can get a stall at the flea market.
我喜欢跳蚤市场  特别独立
I love the flea market. It is so indie.
好主意
That is a great idea.
十分赞
It's just tremendous.
是吧
Right?
平分三份
Three-way split.
是的  当然了
Oh, yeah, sure. Of course.
没问题
No problem.
就和实习一样
It's like an internship.
我叫梅兰妮
I'm Melanie.
好吧
All right, okay.
梅兰妮  这是欧德多莉奥
Uh, Melanie, meet Old Dolio.
老什么
Old... what?
多莉奥
Dolio.
欧德多莉奥
Old Dolio.
好的
Okay.
我喜欢那  我喜欢那
I like that. I like that.
看吧  这就是那种
See, this is exactly the kind of thing
我期待已久的事情
that I've been wanting...
别碰
Don't touch! Ah!
别碰桌子
Don't touch the table.
我曾经历过比这个小很多的地震
I've been through tremors a lot smaller than this.
会让一切东西都带电的  就像  嘶
It just turns everything , like zap.
因为大的震动会这样随之而来
'Cause this is the way the big one starts.
带着噪声  不断地
With the noise, it just keeps
叠加再叠加
building and building and building.
但这次没有
But this one's not building.
大的地震会有很大动静的
The big one will be loud.
如果你够幸运  你会被压碎
I mean, if you're lucky, you'll get crushed.
然后你就会当场死亡
And then you'll... you just die right then and there.
立刻
Immediately.
永无止境的空虚啊
A never-ending void.
所以  只能活一次
So, yolo.
我说的对吧
Am I right?
他们真有个性啊  超级特别
They are real characters, super unique.
但你会保证他们的可靠是吧
But you vouch for them, right?
担保吗
Vouch?
我是说  保证基本安全
I just mean on, like, a level of basic safety.
我曾有个朋友是跳脱衣舞的
I had a friend who did stripping,
我绝不会做那个
and I would never do that,
但这次感觉
but this feels like a little more...
好吧  实话实说
Okay. You know, if I'm being honest,
我最喜欢的电影是十一罗汉系列
my favorite movies are the Ocean Eleven movies.
美国犯罪电影  讲述了超级大盗丹尼·奥申为了重新夺回妻子泰丝\n一夜之间召集十一位行内好手抢劫情敌赌场的故事
能够成为一个真正的抢劫犯
And I just am pretty psyched
我感到超级兴奋
about being on, like, an actual heist.
你是怎么认识他们的
How did you meet them?
那是我的父母
They're my parents.
这件衬衫很有趣
That's an interesting blouse.
谢谢
Thank you.
这其实是条  条裙子
You know, it was actually a-a dress.
并且我只是
And then I just...
我喜欢你的运  运动服
I like your tr-tracksuit.
不是那个抽屉  试试别的抽屉
Not that drawer. Try the other drawer.
苏  你看起来好棒
Sue! You look so great!
我们来了
Here we are.
这些是我  我的家人
This is m-my family.
我喜欢这些  苏
I love these, Sue.
是不是很棒
Aren't they great?
我丈夫给我的
My husband gave them to me.
他在英格兰搞到的
He got them in England.
我父母两边的祖先都来自英国
My ancestors were British on both sides.
我想那边的人要更文明些
I think the people are more civilized there.
-下午茶时间之类的  -这个太好了
- 4:00 tea and all that. - This is great.
苏
Sue.
我好喜欢这个狗
I love this dog.
哎呀
Blimey!
模仿英国口音
我这笨手笨脚真是羞煞人了
I've made a wretched mess, I'm afraid.
哦  无碍母亲
Oh, that's all right, Mum.
无需介怀
No bother, really.
我刚才没发现你们是
I-I didn't realize at first that you were...
但你们不是英国人
But you're not British.
不是
No.
不  你太黑了
No. You're too dark.
哪里都有深肤色的人
There are dark people everywhere.
我知道
I know.
我意思是当你想象一个
I just meant what you think of when you imagine a...
她是收养的  对
She's adopted. Yeah.
我们一直说
We always say
一个是上天赠与的一个是自己选择的
we were given one and we chose one.
就像我对我的小虫虫的感受
That's just how I feel about my Doodlebug.
过来宝贝
Come here, baby. Yeah.
小虫虫  那是个好名字
Doodlebug. That's a beautiful name.
-是不是  -是法语
- Is that... - It's French.
六百五  我们要的是一千五
650? We need 1,500.
我们没想赖账
We don't want to push it.
单次存款超过七百会受到银行检查
Deposits over 700 trigger a bank review,
所以我们得分几次完成
so we'll do this a few more times.
周五前还有两次
Well, two more by Friday.
啥
What?
不行
No.
不  这太  如果我们被抓了
No, this is... If we get caught,
我是波多黎各人情况会更惨
it-it'll be much worse for me because I'm Puerto Rican.
是不是很神奇
Isn't that amazing?
欧德多莉奥在会写字前先学会了模仿笔迹
Old Dolio learned to forge before she learned to write.
实际上她就是这么学会写字的
Well, actually, that's how she did learn to write.
那我的计划呢  难道就
What about my plan? I mean, was that just...
你靠孤独的人发善心而来钱的计划吗
Your plan to cash in on the generosity of lonely people?
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
你把我指甲碰掉了
You knocked off my nail.
我怎么
I... I mean, what am I...
我只能把它们全摘掉了
I'm gonna have to take them all off now,
否则我就会看起来像个
because I'm gonna look like a crazy person
像个少了一个指甲的疯子
with just, like, one nail missing.
你在干什
What are you...?
好吧  我可以
Oh, okay. I can...
你得用  特殊的抛光条才能把它卸干净
You need, like, special nail polish remover for that.
好  好  好好
Oh, uh, yep, yep, yep, yep.
这买卖灵活还回报率超高
This is a very liquid and high-yield deal.
没错  设计的太好了
That's right. It's a nice design. Um...
我都没注意
I mean, I hadn't noticed.
还有点时髦
It's kind of chic.
我想我们应该赶紧把那个给斯托维克
I think we should give that to Stovik right now
-还有告诉他剩下的很快会来  -你吼啊
and tell him the rest is coming. - Howdy-do.
你吼  你吼啊
Howdy-do. Howdy-do.
你吼啊
Howdy-do.
看这哥们儿
Look at this guy.
看这
Look at...
我就像个参议员
I feel like a senator.
我超爱浴缸的
Ah. I love hot tubs.
你的浴室是什么色调的
What color is your bathroom?
你觉得这个会配吗
Do you think this one will match?
有点烟熏  珊瑚色的
This, like, smoky, coraly thing?
等会  你可以直接滑进去
Stop it. You can just slide right in.
进来啊  欧德多莉奥
Come on in, Old Dolio.
我想你不能进去
I don't think you're supposed to get in that.
当然可以
Sure, you can.
这是干试
It's a dry test.
进去试试
Get on in there.
对  您可以随意点儿
Yeah. Just make yourselves comfy.
来  我来扶你
Here, let me, let me help you out.
我  我自己可以
Uh, I... I can do it. I can...
对  没错
Yeah. Yeah.
随便试随便躺
Get yourselves comfortable.
找个位置  这里头大得很
Grab a seat. Plenty to choose from.
好的  现在我需要各位想象
Okay, now, I want you guys to imagine
温暖的水漫到了这儿
hot water right up to here.
好吗  我也一起进来
Okay? I'll get in there with you.
嘿
Hey.
对  抱歉
Yep. Sorry.
47个可调节按摩头
47 adjustable massaging heads
还有颈部和肩膀的冲浪喷嘴
with targeted neck and shoulder jets.
氛围大瀑布  营造舒缓气氛
A cascading waterfall, uh, creating a soothing ambience.
那是个气氛装置
Uh, there's an ambiance.
我应该继续还是
Should I go on or...?
她看上了对吗
She's sold, right?
多少钱
How much is it?
9499  好吗
9,499. Okay?
首付仅150美元  之后月付99
Just $150 down and $99 a month,
加上了29%的利率
with, uh, 29% APR financing.
你是说  我们掏150美元就能把它带走了
So, you... w-we pay $150, we can walk away with it?
没错
Yeah.
并不是这一个
Well, not this exact one.
我们需要从仓库出货
It has to ship from the warehouse.
但是  最迟明天晚上
But by the end of the day tomorrow.
这是150
That's 150.
所以说如果我不满意
Um, so if I'm not happy, uh,
我可以随时把它送回来并且全额退款
I can return it at any point and get a full refund?
一旦安装了  你就没办法
Well, once it's installed, you can't...
安装  对对  安装后  当然了
Oh, ins... yeah. Yeah, yeah. In-Installed, of course.
但是如果还没安装呢
But if it hasn't been installed?
那当然可以
Then sure. Yeah.
比如  如果尺寸不对或者颜色不合适
You know, like, if it doesn't fit or if the color's off.
还有  镀层是选配
And, now, um, the cladding is extra.
我给你个建议
I have a suggestion for you.
什么
What?
多穿点衣服
Wear more clothes.
你让所有人感觉不舒服
You're making everybody feel uncomfortable.
我可以得到全额退款
I'll get a full refund?
好的  咱们速战速决
Okay, we got to be in and out
才能赶上五点的泄露
so we can catch the leak by 5:00.
好的  实话说  我还有点兴奋
Okay. Honestly, I'm kind of excited
因为这男人太瘆人了
because this guy is such a creep.
所以  他的名字是亚伯
So, his name is Abe.
天呐  感觉想在演碟中谍
Oh, God, this feels like Mission: Impossible.
好的  他就是我们所说的"未登机"乘客
Okay. Okay, so he's what we call a no-show.
他没来取走他的眼镜
He didn't pick up his glasses,
所以我只能给他打个提醒电话
so I had to give him a reminder call,
电话里他要求我给他送过来
and when I did, he asked if I can come and deliver,
我说一般来说我们不提供这项服务
which I said normally we wouldn't do that.
但是  当我说我会带上我的家人时
But when I told him that I was bringing my family,
他就  好像哭了
he, like, was crying.
就好像很绝望  就是
Like, so desperate. It was...
门没锁
It's open.
所以我就  直接  好吧
So I just... I just, um... Okay.
你好
Hi.
我不太舒服
I'm not feeling well,
不过  请自便
but, please, make-make yourself at home.
就是这样
That's it.
像在自己家一样就好
Just be how you are at home.
只是在这房子里平常的一天
Just a normal day around the house.
我想他只是太孤单了
I think he's just lonely.
哦  他在假装  他想让我们
Oh, he's pretending. He wants us to...
对  好像我们是他的家人
Right, like we're his family.
两次后击  现在唯一的
two strokes back right now, and the only thing...
对  很好
Good. That's good.
我  我儿子以前就爱看那个
M-My son used to watch that.
Robert  就知道体育的事
Oh, Robert, always with the sports.
你偶尔也去给草坪除下草啊
Why don't you mow the lawn for once?
太好了
Nice.
再来一些
Do more like that.
学校怎么样  宝贝
How was school, hon?
学校挺好的
School was fine.
你今天怎么样
How was your day?
大点声  谢谢
A little louder, please.
你今天怎么样
How was your day?
你今天做了什么  妈妈
What did you do today, Mom?
你问这个  太贴心了
That's nice... to be asked that.
你真的想知道吗
You really want to know?
不太轻松
Wasn't easy.
我的生活没有一天是轻松的
None of my days are easy.
为什么  出什么事了
Why? What happened?
冰箱坏了
The refrigerator broke.
不在这里面
It's not in there.
那么
So, uh...
你一定就是来修冰箱的人了
You must be the refrigerator repair person.
好
Okay.
我打赌你当你外出工作的时候
I bet you meet a lot of lonely women
见过很多孤独的女人
when you're out in the field.
修理冰箱时
Repairing refrigerators.
家庭主妇们肯定爱往你身上扑吧
Housewives must be throwing themselves at you, huh?
因为
'Cause, uh...
你需要工具的话我们这儿有
You know, if you need tools, we have tools.
我只是来工作的
Uh, I'm just here to do a job.
嘿  支票本不在这儿
Hey. Checkbook is not here.
看看他的卧室
Check his bedroom.
快点
Come on.
这太难了
This is hard.
就像  努力想睡着
It's like trying to fall asleep...
再也不醒
forever.
那些听起来很好
It sounds good.
如果有点杯盘叮当
Maybe some silverware clinking.
或者钢琴声
Or play the piano.
我想就在里面  但是我们得等会
I think it's in there, but we have to wait.
已经四点十五了
It's 4:15.
我们会错过泄露的
We'll miss the leak.
他在努力试着
He's trying to...
去死
...die.
但是我们应该继续
But we should, we should keep on, um...
他说他想听钢琴还有餐具的声音
He said he wants piano playing and s-silverware clinking.
学校怎么样  宝贝
How was school, hon?
挺好的
It was fine.
但是我饿坏了
But I'm starving.
我  我也是
M-Me, too.
你想来点剩的蛋糕吗
Would you like some leftover cake?
好啊
Okay.
他得分了吗
He just scored?
他一杆进洞
Oh, he scored a-a one-holer.
我能来点那个吗
Do you think I could have some of that?
你想来点牛奶吗
Would you like some milk?
好的
Please.
谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
我想我明天要修剪草坪
You know, I think I will mow the lawn tomorrow.
你上周末也是这么说的
You said that last weekend.
有吗
Did I?
也许我来修剪草坪吧
Maybe I'll mow the lawn.
我直接去车库把它拿出来
I'll just go into the garage and get it out.
好了
Okay.
去看看
Go check.
去
Go.
我还活着吗
Am I still here?
是的
Yeah.
看到光了吗
You see how there's light?
你就知道了  因为死了周围会很黑
You'll know because it'll be dark all around and...
很静
quiet.
求你了
Please...
不要对房子做任何事
don't do anything to the house.
我的孩子要它有用
My kids have plans for it.
他们并不坏
They're not bad kids.
只是很忙
Just busy.
人生
Life is...
什么都不是
nothing.
不要想太多  随他去吧
Just let it go without really thinking about it.
就像你放开
Like you're letting go of a...
一根琴弦
piece of string.
就让它
Just let it...
没那么大不了
It's not that big of a deal.
不
Oh, no.
天哪
Oh, my God.
怎么了
What's wrong?
还问我怎么了  这
What's wrong? This...
不是  我的意思是
No, I-I mean...
她心软了
She has tender feelings.
你对此一无所知
You wouldn't know anything about that.
我懂
I know.
根本没有支票簿
Oh, there's no checkbook.
会感到悲伤才是你的本性
You're sad is what you are.
什么
Huh?
我不会再这样做了
I'm not gonna do this again.
而且我觉得我们不该拿走他的东西
And-and I don't think that we should take anything from him.
好吧  来都来了
Okay, okay. So here we are.
我也不清楚
Oh, I don't know.
这房子里藏了一本支票簿
Somewhere there's a checkbook in this house,
我们找到它  我们就
and, uh, when we find it, we're just gonna...
我们就把850美元全兑了完事
we're gonna cash out the whole $850 and be done with it,
因为说实话我感觉非常不自在
because, quite frankly, I'm feeling very uncomfortable.
摊上这事我很不安  所以
I've been put in an uncomfortable position, so...
快去拿桶
Go run the buckets.
搭53路还来得及
You can still make it if you take the 53, huh?
去吧  快点
Come on, hurry. Hurry.
我的
Oh, my...
我懂的  好的  不  你坐下
So, I know. Okay. No, no. You sit down.
坐  坐下  喝杯水
S-Sit down, and you have a glass of water and...
此处为赔偿支票  收款人欧德多莉奥·达因  金额$1575
你儿子几岁来着
And your son is how old?
三岁
Three.
他的名字是
And his name is?
赛勒斯  小赛
Cyrus. Cy.
好吧
Okay.
你好  小赛
Hi, Cy.
他也会  尤其是和新朋友一起
I mean, he would, too, uh, especially with new people.
他会暴躁
I mean, he just goes ballistic.
好吧
It's... Okay.
很好
Okay, that's good.
所以我们现在有个案例
So, we know now that we have
一个三岁小孩老是打人
a three-year-old that tends to hit.
好吧  那也很正常
Okay. That's not abnormal.
所以一开始  我只是观察
So, first, I'll just observe.
-好吗  -好
- Okay?  - All right.
你  饿吗
Are you... hungry?
不
Mm, no.
累了吗
Are you tired?
不
Mm... no.
你看起来很兴奋  小赛
You look excited, Cy.
见到其他小朋友是不是很高兴
Are you excited to see the other children?
-你是不是只想要他们注意到你  -是的
- Do you just need some of their attention?  - Yeah.
那就对了
Yeah! Okay.
有时这就足够了
And sometimes that's enough.
只要嘴上说出需要就足够了
Just verbalizing the need is enough.
一个三岁小孩想要别人关心
A three-year-old that wants attention...
并非无理取闹  对吗
not unreasonable, right?
欧德多莉奥
Old Dolio.
你应该  如果你想的话
You should... well, if you want to.
她可能会再干一票的
She might do one more.
不
No.
不如我们一起干
How about we do it together?
或许你来给这场派对开头吧
Maybe you get the party started.
我就出去下  看看前  前面
I'll just go, uh, check the-the front.
好的
Okay.
我想欧德多莉奥不喜欢我
I don't think Old Dolio likes me.
是的  她谁也不喜欢
Oh. No, she-she, she doesn't like anyone.
她平时不是那样的
She's not like that.
你女儿的名字是
And your daughter's name is?
欧德多莉奥
Old Dolio.
欧德什么
Uh, Old...?
多莉奥  我们给她改了个
Dolio. We named her after a homeless guy
中彩票的流浪汉的名  希望她能继承遗产
who won the lottery, hoping he'd put her in his will.
可惜欧德多莉奥  原来的那个欧德多莉奥
But Old Dolio... the old Old Dolio...
最后在试验性的抗癌治理上
used up all his money at the very end
花光了他所有的钱
on experimental cancer stuff.
好吧
Mm. Okay.
你女儿是
And your daughter is...?
她心里没有一丝柔情
She doesn't know anything about tender feelings.
你好  欧德多莉奥
Hi, Old Dolio.
好  我只要观察
Okay, so I'm just gonna observe.
你是否感受到有压力
Are you feeling stressed?
没有
Hmm, no. No.
你想要握着我的手吗
Do you want to hold my hand?
不想吗  没事
No? Okay.
好的
Okay. Hmm.
你的头发可真长
Your hair has gotten so long.
很漂亮  亲爱的
It's beautiful, hon.
我可以摸一摸吗
Can I brush it?
小地震而已  没事的
It's just a tremor. It's okay.
你  没事的
You're... It's okay.
有我在没事的
You're okay with me.
来  让我来调热一点
Here, let's, uh, warm it up a little bit.
是不是有
Is there...?
是有个排水口
Oh, uh, there's a drain.
它可以排水的  下面有个排水口
It can drain. There's a drain under there.
在地上  在地板里
On the floor. In the floor.
所以你是要把它退回去还是卖掉再退回去
So are you gonna return it or sell it and then return it?
还是想怎么样
Or what do you want?
还是关了灯比较好
It's better with the light off.
我们洗个澡吧
Let's take a bath.
惊到你了吗
Are you surprised?
也许你不清楚我的这种感觉
Maybe you didn't know that I-I felt this way.
不
No.
这是我这辈子最不惊讶的事了
I'm the least surprised I've ever been in my life.
所以接下来要干什么
So what's the plan?
你看着我脱衣服  然后开始
You'll watch me undress, and then you'll start
把你老二弄硬  然后我再进来吗
getting your dick hard, then I'll get in?
怎样
Well?
来吧
Come on.
你在想象着什么
So, what were you picturing?
-滑溜的奶子吗  -是的
- Soapy titties? - Sure.
是吗  那肯定
Yeah? Sure.
这能用吗
Does this work?
才不会  对吧  当然是不能用的
No, right? Of course it doesn't work.
凭什么能用
Why would it work?
这里没有一件东西能用
Nothing works here.
真可悲
Pathetic.
那么  乳交吗
So, titty fuck?
-说那你就来劲了  -我要进来了
- Oh, that got your attention. - Knock, knock.
我们这是想要你也开心
We want this to be about your pleasure, too.
是的
Oh, yeah.
那你要怎样才开心
Well, what makes you feel good?
-梅兰妮  别这样  -听我说
Uh, Melanie, uh, let's not... - Listen, uh...
-我们  -我们很惊讶
- Just... let's just... - We-We're, we're surprised.
-吃点点心好吗  -我觉得  我觉得
- Time for a snack, all right? - I think, I think...
-干嘛  -干嘛
- What? - What?
你们在干什么
What are you guys doing?
为什么拿着盘饼干
Why-why are there crackers on a plate?
别走  亲爱的
Don't go, hon.
"亲爱的"
"Hon"?
你刚
You just...
你从来没有那样叫过我
You've never called me that.
我有
I have.
我叫过
I have called you that.
是吗
Oh?
那叫我"亲爱的"
Call me "hon," then.
那是什么
What is that? Hmm?
这是什么  "从出生到十八岁"
What is this? "Newborn to 18 years."
你做不到
You can't do it.
要是工作你就做得到了是吧
I bet you could if it was a job, though, right?
我出1575块让你叫我"亲爱的"
$1,575 to call me "hon."
平分三份
Oh, three-way split.
每人525
It's 525 each.
这次我不想那样做
I don't want to do it that way this time.
就一句  说就是了
It's one word. Just say it.
你就说吧
You could just say it.
我不能就这样说出来
I can't just say it.
我们不会叫你"亲爱的"
We... don't call you "hon"
或者"甜心"或者"宝贝"什么的
or "sweetheart" or "baby."
我们也不会用丝带包什么生日礼物
We don't wrap up little birthday presents with ribbons.
-我  我不是想要  -想的
- I-I don't want... - Yes.
那就是你想要的
That's what you want.
还有什么
And-and what else? Hmm?
要我把你放在肚子上吗
Want me to put you on my abdomen?
做薄煎饼吗
Make pancakes?
还要我跳支小舞吗
And you want me to do a little dance?
-不是  -是的
- No. - Yes.
你想要我们成为虚情假意的人
You want us to be false, fakey people.
是吧
Hmm?
对不起  我不是故意
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to...
我来
I'll do it.
我可以为了1575美金叫你"亲爱的"
I'll call you "hon" for $1,575.
继续走
Keep walking.
继续走  继续走
Keep walking. Keep walking.
东西真多
A lot of stuff.
是的
Yeah. Yeah.
这是什么
What's this?
这是个保暖杯垫
Uh, it's a... it's a mug warmer.
很多时候我妈会买两份东西
A lot of the times, my mom will buy two of something
就给我寄一份
and just send me one.
今天是周三
It's Wednesday.
周三时会漏三倍因为下水道的问题
Wednesday it leaks three times 'cause of sanitation.
这活真的要三个人干
It's... it's really a three-person job.
现在应该流得满地都是了
It's all over the floor now.
他们把桶放好后
They'll be calling any second.
随时都会打过来
Just after they put the buckets down.
好吧
Okay, uh...
总之谢谢你
thank you or whatever.
给你
Um, here.
这应该够付刚刚的
This should cover that.
除非你是批发价买的  我不知道
Unless you bought it in bulk... I don't know.
你  你不用付
Y-You don't pay for...
好吧
Okay.
你在沉迷
You're jonesing.
什么
What?
你对他们上瘾了
You're addicted to them.
我表兄弟提摩西
My cousin Timothy...
当他试着戒毒时  他会先好一些
when he was trying to kick pills, he would be fine,
然后又忽然药瘾
and then he would have this sudden wave
发作得很厉害
of needing them really bad.
但我觉得这有点不一样
Well, I think this is a little different
因为他们是我的父母
because they're my parents.
在哪一点上
In what sense?
什么
What?
在哪一点上他们是你的父母
In what sense are they your parents?
例如呢
What's an example?
在我很小时
We split everything three ways.
我们就什么都分三份
We have since I was little.
那你怎么花你那份的
What do you spend yours on?
你应得的那份
Your third.
我  我们什么都分得特别公平
W-We go in on everything equally.
实际上  那是另一回事
Actually, that's another example.
这是两码事
That makes two things.
你是不是忘记什么了
Aren't you forgetting something?
亲爱的
Hon.
Oh, hon.
我的甜心儿
My sweetheart.
我的小棉袄
My sweet baby.
街对面有个支票兑现的地方
There's a check cashing place across the street.
所以你这是要去
Oh, so you're just gonna go...?
回家
Home.
等  等一下
W-Wait.
你以为我要这么多钱就为了
You thought I was gonna take this much for...?
我是一条龙服务的
This is a full-service deal.
所以
Uh... so...
"我们不叫你'亲爱的'"
"We don't call you 'hon,'
'甜心'或者'宝贝'"
'sweetheart' or 'baby.'"
我叫了
Did that.
"我们不做"
"We don't make..."
薄煎饼
Pancakes?
我们不用非得
We don't have to...
你收下就是了
You can just take it.
她说把你放在肚子上
What was that thing that she said
那是什么来的
about putting you on her abdomen?
那叫乳房爬行
Oh, it's-it's called a breast crawl.
那不是
It's not...
跳支小舞
Uh, do a little dance?
我不懂她为什么说这个
I don't know why she said that.
你跳过舞吗
Have you ever danced?
跳过
Yeah.
生日
Birthdays?
精致漂亮的生日礼物
Birthday presents wrapped up with a bow.
听着  我们别
Look, let's not...
所以我们做完这些事后
So when we've done these things,
我要拿到我的钱  然后你也可以离开了
then I want my money and you can go.
我要去准备明早的薄饼
I have to get pancake stuff for the morning.
早上
The morning?
薄煎饼一般都早上吃
They're a morning thing.
前面有个监控
There's a camera there,
那里和那里
there and there.
所有超一流的保安系统都是五星阵型的
All Super A security systems are on a pentagram,
所以你要卡死角
so you have to move between the points.
通常所有单数过道的商品都是免费的
Basically, all the odd-numbered aisles are free goods.
我是来买东西的  所以
I'm buying this stuff, so...
当然
Yeah.
一个有趣的事实罢了
It's just an... interesting fact.
这样可以吗
Is that okay?
你是想  我有睡衣
Oh. Do you want to... I have pajamas.
不用了  这样就行了
No. I'm good.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
什么意思
What do you mean?
这是
What are...
你是想
Are you trying to...
惹我生气
rile me up?
怎样才能把它弄平了
How does this even work?
我不能
I can't...
这里的话我会这么做  搞个大的即可
Here's what I would do: just one big one.
不用翻那么多次
It's less flipping.
当然  不过小一点会  会很有趣
Yeah, but l-little things are... Like, it-it's fun.
你可以把它们叠起来
You just stack them. Boop.
很多小快乐都是一些没意义的事
Most happiness comes from, like, dumb things.
好吧
Okay.
好的  所以
Okay, uh, so...
薄煎饼做完了
that's that.
什么是  我不
What's, uh... I don't...
这个
Oh, that.
我从个暗点的空间里爬出来就是了
I could just crawl out of a dark space to do that.
这很简单
That's fine.
所以  这应该是全黑的  然后我爬出来
So, it'll be all dark, and then I'll crawl out.
光线会很刺眼
The light will be blinding.
这个就当作是腹部了
And this is the abdomen.
然后我们就完成了
And then we're done.
我知道一个比这更暗的地方
I know a place that's darker than this.
这里就可以了  行得通的
This is fine. It'll work.
不会很费时间的
It's not gonna take long.
我们刚经过了有7路的站台
Oh, we're right by the 7.
回来的时候你可以顺路把我放这
You could just drop me on the way back.
这是
This is the...
灯坏了
Light's broken.
这这是挺黑的  但是
Well, it's... it's dark, but...
就这样了
but this was so far.
我们现在来完成它
We could've been done by now.
没错
Exactly.
好吧  那我就爬出来然后
Okay, so I guess I'll crawl out and...
这只是个小地震
It's just a tremor.
不  这是
No. This one is...
它在变强
This one is building.
开始地震了
Whoa! It's happening!
-出去  快出去  -不  不  别动
- Out. Get out. - No! No, no, no, no.
别碰门或者墙
Don't touch the door or the walls.
一切都带着电  呆在中间就好
Everything is live. Just stay in the middle.
-这是门把手吗  -这是金属  它有电
- Is the doorknob... - It's metal. It's live.
别碰它  别碰
Don't touch it. Don't touch.
好安静
It's so quiet.
一点声都没有
I don't hear anyone.
是很安静
It is quiet.
为什么这么安静
Why is it so quiet?
更黑了
It's darker.
这里之前就是黑的
It was dark before.
不  现在彻底黑了
No, it's completely black.
我的天呐
Oh, my God.
什么
What?
Oh. What?
你不会想知道的
You don't want to know.
我们不再活着了
We're not in life anymore.
-什么  -真的
- What? - Yeah.
我认为它立马就发生了
I think it happened right away.
就在第一声巨响之后
Right after that first big noise.
-它  -我们死了
- It? - We died.
什  我没事  我
Wh... I'm fine. I...
这之后每个人都这么说
That's what everyone always says right after.
他们无法相信这
They can't believe it.
你可能相信不了  但它刚刚就发生了
You might never believe it, but this is just how it's gonna be.
永远地
Forever.
只有我们
Just us.
-在黑暗之中  -别说了  这不是
- In blackness. - Stop. That's not...
你不会相信的
You can't believe it
因为你深爱着生活
because you were married to life.
沉迷于此
Hooked on it.
我并不留恋  所以对我来说这没什么的
I wasn't hooked, so it's not such a big deal to me.
-这会很伤心  -我不觉得
- It would hurt. - I don't think so.
拜托  不要这样
Please. Stop.
我能摸到我的脸
I can feel my face.
是的  那只是记忆触感
Yeah. That's just a memory.
我没什么好遗憾的
I don't have any regrets.
虽然你会很遗憾
You're gonna have regrets, though,
因为你再也不能做爱  跳舞和吃薄煎饼了
because you're gonna miss sex and dancing and pancakes.
我刚只吃了一个薄煎饼  所以我不会伤心
I just had that one pancake, so I'm not gonna be sad.
你  你照了那么多次镜子
You-you looked in the mirror so many times
你再也看不到你的脸了
you'll miss your face forever.
但我  我甚至没
But I-I don't even...
我  我甚至记不住我的脸
I-I don't even remember my face.
我都说不出我长得怎样
I can't even say what I looked like.
你有着长长的浅金色头发
You had long, sandy blond hair...
-嘘  -透蓝色的眼睛和
- Shh. ... - ice blue eyes and...
别说了  嘘
Stop. Shh.
-这都不重要  -还有纯白的皮肤
- Just doesn't matter. - And pure skin.
你知道我本来想要抢劫你
You know I was just trying to rob you.
不
No.
你真的是蠢的要命
You're such a stupid little idiot,
简直脑袋长奶头上
and your brain is in your tits!
原计划是我过去  然后
The plan was for me to go, and then...
然后在你公寓监视着
and-and stake out your apartment
然  然后要你的银行卡密码
and-and get access to your account...
你们没事吧
You guys fine?
没事  你呢
Yeah. Are you?
好着呢
Yeah.
我本来  我本来在开车
I was, I was driving.
所有人都停下来了  太疯狂了
Everyone stopped. It was crazy.
我们以为自己死了
We thought we were dead.
我不那么想
I didn't think that.
我是欧德多莉奥
I'm Old Dolio.
见到你真是太好了
It's wonderful to meet you.
愿主保佑你
God bless you.
好吧  我  我不信教  但
Okay, I'm-I'm not religious, but, uh...
对  我  我也不信
No, I'm-I'm not, either.
我之前从来不会这么说
I've never said that before in my life.
那这样呢
How about this?
对吧  你觉得那是次大的吗
Right? You think that was the big one?
我说不准
Uh, I don't know.
-我不觉得那  -不  它是的
- I don't think that. - No, it was.
就是这么回事
That was it.
谢谢你
Thank you.
-谢谢  -好的
- Thank you. - Oh. Right.
握  握够了
This is, this is done.
我永远都不会忘记你
Uh... I'm never gonna forget you.
一辈子
My whole life.
这  这是斯巴鲁
This... this Subaru.
我记住这一切了
I've memorized all of this.
好吧  我们可以
Okay, can we...
你们没事吧
You guys okay?
没事  你还好吗
Yes. How are you?
我没事
Oh, I'm fine.
对  这店很扛震的
Yeah, these are great structures for quakes.
因为我们24小时营业  我们得随时准备着
Since we're open 24 hours, we got to be ready for anything.
这店里的东西你都用过吗
Have you tried everything in this store?
没啊
Nope.
如果我在这工作  我就会这么做
That's what I would do if I worked here.
现在做还不晚
It's not too late.
你可以每个都试一遍  然后找出你的最爱
You can try everything once and then isolate your favorites
然后  选个好日子吃掉它们
and-and just eat them on a perfect day
在你通常吃美食的地方
where you just eat all your favorite foods.
如果我在这工作  我也会这么干的
That's what I would do if I worked here.
所以  你这能申请吗
So, do you apply?
怎样才能在这工作呢
Or how does that work?
你们需要经过特殊训练吗
Do you have to take special training
是上个课还是什么啊
or-or a class or something?
没错  没错
Yes! Yes!
快进来  快进来
Come in! Come in!
我要  我要挤爆这个
I'm gonna, I'm gonna pop this.
你就这么打开这个的  对吗
That's how you open it, right?
就直接挤爆这个
You just... pop.
一共是29.83
Okay, that comes to 29.83.
这可是我的钱
That's my money.
那  我不买了  其实
So, no sale, actually.
我应该放回去吗
Uh, should I put all this back?
我还是  还是  直接走吧
I'm-I'm just gonna... I'm gonna, I'm gonna leave.
我走了
I'm gonna... Okay.
我甚至都
You know, I-I didn't even...
我把整件事情给忘掉了
I forgot about that whole thing.
那你忘记抢我钱了吗
Did you forget about robbing me?
你忘记你想抢我钱啦
You forget that you wanted to rob me?
你想进入我的账户  还记得吗
Wanted to gain access to my account, remember?
我脑子长奶头上吗
My brain is in my tits?
不
No.
那只是个谎言  是个谎言
Th-That was just, that was just a lie.
你  你不信我
Y-You don't believe me.
不  我信你
No, I believe you.
你不信
You don't.
那我怎么办啊  好吧
Well, what do I do? Okay.
-我能做  -我刚把铃声关了
- What can I... - The ringer was off.
-妈妈  我没事  -你没事的
- I'm fine, Mom. - You're okay.
-你还好吗  -我没事  -这里
- You're okay? - Yeah, I'm okay. - Uh, here.
我会  你想让我  天呐
I'll... You want me to... Oh, my God.
-我要用这个砸手指  -你没问题吗
- I'll smash my finger with this! - Are you all right?
-我现在就要砸了  -那确实很震惊
- I'll do it! Right. - That was big.
我一听说就打电话过去了
I called the second I heard.
-我打了好多次  -回来
- I've been calling and calling and... - Come back.
-我很抱歉  -我的心还在乱跳
- I'm sorry. - Oh, my heart is still pounding.
我根本不知道我应该干什么
I don't know what to do.
-那真是太  -我到底应该干什么
- It was just so... - I don't know what to do.
-我在干啥  我在干啥  -我需要冷静一下
- What do I do? What do I do? - I could use a squeeze.
-冷静  冷静  妈妈  -我不知道该干什么
- Squeeze, squeeze, Mama. - I don't know what to do.
我很抱歉  我
I'm sorry. I...
什么
What is...
你后面有什么
What is that behind you?
或许你可以
Maybe you should...
-好的  -好
-Okay. -Okay.
谢谢你等我
Thank you for waiting.
很快就会有人来找你
Someone will be with you shortly.
他们从不接人
They never pick up, so...
如果你不想的话就不用这样做
You don't have to do it if you don't want to.
就像是如果你不
It's like, if you don't...
欧德多莉奥  听到我们了吗
Old Dolio? Can you hear us?
我们打了  打了很多次电话
We've been, we've been calling and calling and calling.
就是那个
That was it.
那是次大地震
It was the big one.
你还好吗
You okay?
你现在还没准备好开口
You're not ready to talk yet.
没关系
That's okay.
就让他们待这
Just leave them here.
我明白了  好的
I am. Okay.
拜拜
Bye-bye.
"生日快乐
"Happy birthday.
我们的小公主14了  爱你的"
Our little girl is 14. Love..."
刚出生
Newborn.
1岁  2岁  3岁  4岁  5岁  6岁
One, two, three, four, five, six,
7岁  8岁  9岁  10岁
seven, eight, nine, ten,
11  12  13  14  15  16  17
11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17.
第18个在哪里
Where's the 18th one?
都是垃圾
This is crap.
你明白的  它们就是
You know they're just...
就像是某种任务
I know it's some kind of job.
他们在扰乱我
They're scamming me.
"生日快乐
"Happy birthday.
我们的小公主18岁了
Our little girl is 18.
诚挚的邀请"
Cordially invite..."
他们想带我出去吃晚餐
They want to take me out to dinner.
我们俩
Both of us.
在Mé莉塞
At Mélisse.
为了庆祝我18岁生日
It's for my 18th birthday.
这是你的生日吗
Is it your birthday?
不  我今年26了
No. And I'm 26.
别去  行吗
Don't go, right?
我必须去
I have to. No.
不不不  你不需要
No, no, no. You actually... But you don't. You...
那就把钱留下来
Then leave the money here.
我只是为了确保他们不会
Just to make sure that they don't...
他们认为我一无所知
They think I don't know anything
关于这样一个高档餐厅
about a sort of fancy restaurant like that.
那我们就走进那里  让他们大为震惊
Well, we're gonna walk in there and they're gonna be like,
"你现在到底是谁"
"Whoa. Who even are you now?"
嗨  我们约了另外两位
Hi. We're meeting two others.
可能在达因下面
Could be under Dyne.
他们很可能迟到  有三站路呢
They're probably gonna be late. It's three bus rides.
不啊
Nope.
我通常更喜欢坐在后面
I usually like to sit more in the back,
但今天这桌没关系
but this table's fine.
谢谢
Thank you.
要开始来点饮料吗
Can I start you off with some drinks?
好
Uh, yes.
我想要  你们还有波特酒吗
I'll have, uh... Do you still have the port?
谷物波特酒还是20年茶色波特酒啊
The Colheita or the tawny 20-year?
那就谷物波特酒
Um, the, uh, the-the Colheita.
我  我想想  我要
I-I guess I'll... I will have
"古物伯特酒"
um, the "Golaca..."
实际上  啥也不要  来杯水
Uh, actually, nothing. Water.
这不就是那个给你按摩的女士吗
Oh, isn't that the woman who gave you the massage?
嗨
Oh, hi.
Hi.
治愈人的艺术
The healing arts.
是个稳定的职业
That's a solid profession.
人们经常身体酸痛
People are always in pain.
那么  梅兰妮  你父母是干什么的呢
So, what do your parents do, Melanie?
我妈在房地产工作
My mom works in real estate.
罗伯特以前
Oh, Robert used to...
我以前是出版
I used to publish a, uh,
一本面向房地产中介的资源指南
resource guide for real estate agents.
对  里面还有优惠券
Yeah. With coupons.
那时候我们非常坦诚正直
We were straight shooters back then.
我的意思是  如果我们完全诚实
I mean, if we're being completely honest, we...
那真是个艰难的时期
Well, it was tough times.
那本优惠券书并没有起作用
And, you know, the coupon book didn't really take.
我们也算是对时代的回应
Well, we were reacting to the era.
以前每个人都是
Uh, everybody was.
我能看看那本优惠券书吗
Could I see the coupon book?
当然   然后环境改变了
Of course, then the culture changed,
所以现在 我们看起来有点不合拍
and so now we look sort of out of step.
或许还会改回去呢
Oh, maybe it'll change back.
世事可变
It's returnable.
♪ 祝你生日快乐 ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ 祝亲爱的欧德多莉奥生日快乐 ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Old Dolio ♪
♪ 祝你生日快乐 ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you. ♪
36个小时以前  我
36 hours ago, I...
抱歉
Sorry.
我们对你发火了
We were very angry at you.
现在我认为当时只是一个最原始的反应
But, um, I see now that it was just a base response.
只有害怕  真的
It was just fear, really.
只是害怕
Just fear.
在那件事情发生后  我
And then, after the big one happened, I...
这很艰难
This is hard.
我表达的不好
I'm not good at this.
在那之后  我们很担心
After the... I... we got very worried.
我们认为你没去世
We didn't think you were dead,
但是假如你去世了
but if you were dead...
我会非常后悔没有
I would have regretted not...
做足够的事情  来告诉你
...doing enough things to show you...
因为  我不知道  我只是
See, because, I don't know, I just...
我之前一直以为这很无礼
um, I just... I always thought it was insulting
把你当成还没长大的小孩
to treat you like a child.
这听起来很不真诚
It just, it just always seemed so insincere.
我以为我们都认同这样做
And-and I thought we agreed on that.
你明白吗
You know?
但是  当
Um, but when, um...
在那之后
after the...
我一直在思考  我只想
the thing I just kept thinking is I just want to,
我只想捧着她的脸
I just want to hold her face.
我们能有你真的很幸运
We've been very lucky to have you.
老天
Oh, God.
我们真的非常非常幸运能有你这个女儿
We are very, very lucky to have you as our daughter.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我真的很抱歉
I'm just sorry.
嗨
Hey.
晚安  亲爱的女儿
Good night, sweet daughter.
做个好梦
Have sweet dreams.
明天早上  如果你想吃的话
Um, in the morning, if you want, uh...
我能做些薄煎饼
I can make pancakes.
明天是礼拜五
T-Tomorrow's Friday.
那张支票
The check.
我们把钱取出来了  但是没花
We cashed it, but we haven't spent it.
别担心租金
Don't worry about the rent.
我们是你的父母
We're the parents.
我们会解决的
We'll handle it.
我们有个计划
We've got a plan.
好的
Okay.
那我就
Um, I guess I'll s...
明天再见你
...see you tomorrow.
好  好滴
Yeah. Yep.
如果它离开了
So, if it's gone,
他们是怪物  这整个晚上就是个谎言
they're monsters and this whole night was a lie.
明白吗
Okay?
但如果他们都在那里  他们就是真实的
But if it's there, then this is all real.
你会相信的
You'll believe that.
等等  等等
Wait, wait. Um...
如果这只是我的那第三份  525
If it's just my third, 525...
意味着
...then that means...
"我们只能成为现在的自己
We can only ever be how we are.
但是我们爱你
But we love you and, um...
我们希望你一切都好"
...we wish you well."
都在这了
It's all there.
明天我可能会在你起床之前早早离开
I'll probably take off early tomorrow before you're up.
谢谢你做的一切
Thank you for everything.
真的
Really.
没问题
No problem.
所以呢
So what?
什么
What?
退款一共485.05
Okay, so your refund comes to 485.05.